Guide to the Office of Alumni Relations records, 1848-2005 RG0026
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photos from old events, 1965-1992; RG0026 Series 10; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  - Reunion 1991, Carnival on the Quad, Smith Center [3/3], 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.18)
  - Reunion 1991, 1971 Party, 25 Yr. Party, 1981 Party, 04/12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.19)
  - Reunion 1991, Carnival on the Quad; Smith Center, 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 26.2)
  - Reunion 1991, Class of 1986, undated (Box 1, Folder 26.21)
  - OAR, GAA, EXEC, ARC Photos, Groups, undated (Box 1, Folder 27.1)
  - OAR, GAA, EXEC, ARC Photos, Groups, undated (Box 1, Folder 27.2)
  - OAR, GAA, EXEC, ARC Photos, Alumni Relations Council (GWU) [1/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.3)
  - OAR, GAA, EXEC, ARC Photos, Alumni Relations Council (GWU) [2/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.4)
  - OAR, GAA, EXEC, ARC Photos, Office of Alumni Relations Staff [1/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.5)
  - OAR, GAA, EXEC, ARC Photos, Office of Alumni Relations Staff [2/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.6)
  - OAR, GAA, EXEC, ARC Photos, Executive Committee-General, 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.7)
  - General Alumni Association, Alumni Relations Council, GWU [1/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.8)
  - General Alumni Association, Alumni Relations Council, GWU [2/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.9)
  - General Alumni Association, Office of Alumni Relations Staff [1/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.1)
  - General Alumni Association, Office of Alumni Relations Staff [2/2], 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.11)
  - The George Washington University, 10/02/1990 (Box 1, Folder 27.12)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [1/3], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 28.1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [2/3], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 28.2)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [3/3], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 28.3)
  - Jack Morton Alumni Lounge Dedication [1/3], 04/23/1990 (Box 1, Folder 29.1)
  - Jack Morton Alumni Lounge Dedication [2/3], 04/23/1990 (Box 1, Folder 29.2)
  - Jack Morton Alumni Lounge Dedication [3/3], 04/23/1990 (Box 1, Folder 29.3)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [1/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [2/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.2)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [3/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.3)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [4/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.4)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [5/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.5)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [6/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.6)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [7/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.7)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [8/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.8)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [9/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.9)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Dinner [10/10], 02/17/1990 (Box 1, Folder 30.1)
  - David Eisenhower Reception [1/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 31.1)
  - David Eisenhower Reception [1/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 31.2)
  - David Eisenhower Reception [1/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 31.3)
  - Dean Mickey East- ESIA, undated (Box 1, Folder 32.1)
  - Alumni Service Awards, Marvin Center Ballroom, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 33.1)
  - Trainer George, Alumni Service Awards, Woodlawn Plantation, 06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 34.1)
  - Nancy Thompson, Alumni Service Awards, 06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 34.2)
  - Bucky Herzog, Alumni Service Awards, 06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 34.3)
  - Admiral Coclough, Alumni Service Awards, 06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 34.4)
  - Edward A. Wareham, Alumni Service Awards, 06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 34.5)
  - Howard O. Johnson, Alumni Service Awards, 06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 34.6)
  - Distinguished Alumni Scholar, Harden McConnell [1/2], 10/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 35.1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Scholar, Harden McConnell [2/2], 10/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 35.2)
  - Distinguished Alumni Scholar, Andrea Foster, Michael Karnen, 10/26/1987 (Box 1, Folder 35.3)
  - Alumni Reunion, President's Reception, 06/07/1986 (Box 1, Folder 36.1)
  - Alumni Reunion, Carol Snow Plew with father Richard Snow, 06/16/1986 (Box 1, Folder 36.2)
  - GAA Officers, Board Meeting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 37.1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Recipients, Luther Brady [1/3], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38.1)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Recipients, Luther Brady [2/3], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38.2)
  - Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Recipients, Luther Brady [3/3], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38.3)
  - Elmor T. Brooks, NASA Headquarters, Washington D.C., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 38.4)
  - Sidney Dewberry, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38.5)
  - Earle Harbison, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38.6)
  - Richard Wallis, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38.7)
  - Pastor Farinas and his wife dancing, Alumni Service Awards, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.1)
  - Everette A. MacIntyre, with his wife Reta, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.2)
  - Lt. Col. William D. Sterrett dancing w. Laura Tardiff-Cruit, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.3)
  - C. Oscar Berry, Law '32, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.4)
  - Reunion Picnic, alumni and students, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.5)
  - Elmer Louis Kayser, Genevieve Riviere, Walter E. Barton, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.6)
  - Luise H. Bishop and Harold W. Curran, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.7)
  - C. Oscar Berry & Kay Russell, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.8)
  - Jesse R. Smith, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.9)
  - S. John, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.1)
  - Saturday Evening Dinner Dance, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.11)
  - Harold Sangster at BBA, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.12)
  - Louise Bishop Harold Curran at Friday Luncheon, 04/23/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.13)
  - Dr. Paul Malone, Saturday Evening, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.14)
  - Jack O'Shean, Saturday Evening, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.15)
  - Roscoe Egger, IRS Commissioner, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.16)
  - Saturday Evening Dinner Dance, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.17)
  - Saturday Evening Dinner Dance, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.18)
  - Columbian Women Tea, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.19)
  - Reunion Weekend, Dinner Dance, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.2)
  - Ann J. Avery, Pauline H. Dupuy, President Lloyd Elliott, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.21)
  - Saturday BBQ, 04/24/1982 (Box 1, Folder 39.22)
  - Alumni Reunion - 50 year, 06/06/1986 (Box 1, Folder 40.1)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Water Polo [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 41.1)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Water Polo [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 41.2)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Male basketball player, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.3)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, President Elliott with two alumni, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.4)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Group of alumnus, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.5)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Alumni Chatting, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.6)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Group of alumni, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.7)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Soccer match, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.8)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Basketball match [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 41.9)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Basketball match [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 41.1)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Wrestling, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.11)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Edward B. Liles/Law & guest, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.12)
  - Schedule of Alumni Events, Group of alumni, undated (Box 2, Folder 41.13)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [1/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.1)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [2/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.2)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [3/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.3)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [4/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.4)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [5/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.5)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [6/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.6)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [7/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.7)
  - DAA Site, Proposed [8/8], undated (Box 2, Folder 42.8)
  - Swearing In Ceremony, 01/1991 (Box 2, Folder 43.1)
  - Tracing Our Heritage Tour, Fredericksburg, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 44.1)
  - Lucernel Chapel bridge, Tour photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 45.1)
  - Leverick Bay, Virgin Gorda [1/2], 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.2)
  - Leverick Bay, Virgin Gorda [2/2], 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.3)
  - Coming into Roadtown, Tortola, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.4)
  - Charlotte Amalie Harbor, St. Thomas, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.5)
  - 1829 Amalie Harbor - St. Thomas Hotel, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.6)
  - Charlotte Amalie, St. Thomas, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.7)
  - Dock at St. John, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.8)
  - Cruz Bay, St. John, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.9)
  - Sopers Hole, Tortola, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.1)
  - White Bay, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.11)
  - GW gathering on Board, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.12)
  - Santa Cruz de Tenerife, Tenerife Canary Islands, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.13)
  - Rahine River, 06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 45.14)
  - Fame & Football, Reception [1/6], 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 46.1)
  - Fame & Football, Reception [2/6], 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 46.2)
  - Fame & Football, Reception [3/6], 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 46.3)
  - Fame & Football, Reception [4/6], 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 46.4)
  - Fame & Football, Reception [5/6], 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 46.5)
  - Fame & Football, Reception [6/6], 09/30/1991 (Box 2, Folder 46.6)
  - Top Hat Negative, Pres. Trachtenberg by Peg Callahan [1/2], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 47.1)
  - Top Hat Negative, Pres. Trachtenberg by Peg Callahan [2/2], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 47.2)
  - Service Award [1/4], 10/29/1991 (Box 2, Folder 48.1)
  - Service Award [2/4], 10/29/1991 (Box 2, Folder 48.2)
  - Service Award [3/4], 10/29/1991 (Box 2, Folder 48.3)
  - Service Award [4/4], 10/29/1991 (Box 2, Folder 48.4)
  - Service Awards Reception [1/6], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49.1)
  - Service Awards Reception [2/6], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49.2)
  - Service Awards Reception [3/6], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49.3)
  - Service Awards Reception [4/6], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49.4)
  - Service Awards Reception [5/6], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49.5)
  - Service Awards Reception [6/6], 1991 (Box 2, Folder 49.6)
  - Reunion Class '54, Reunion Committee [1/3], 01/1994 (Box 2, Folder 50.1)
  - Reunion Class '54, Reunion Committee [2/3], 01/1994 (Box 2, Folder 50.2)
  - Reunion Class '54, Reunion Committee [2/3], 01/1994 (Box 2, Folder 50.3)
  - Mary Wilson, Reunion Brochure, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 51.1)
  - Reunion Brochure, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 51.2)
  - Homecoming [1/6], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52.1)
  - Homecoming [2/6], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52.2)
  - Homecoming [3/6], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52.3)
  - Homecoming [4/6], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52.4)
  - Homecoming [5/6], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52.5)
  - Homecoming [6/6], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52.6)
  - DAAA Officers "In an election year...", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 53.1)
  - Robert C. Elliott, NYC Alumnus of the Year, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 54.1)
  - Invitation Card, NYC Alumnus of the Year, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 54.2)
  - Craftsmanship, GWU - Alumni [1/7], undated (Box 2, Folder 55.1)
  - Craftsmanship, GWU - Alumni [2/7], undated (Box 2, Folder 55.2)
  - Craftsmanship, GWU - Alumni [3/7], undated (Box 2, Folder 55.3)
  - Craftsmanship, GWU - Alumni [4/7], undated (Box 2, Folder 55.4)
  - Craftsmanship, GWU - Alumni [5/7], undated (Box 2, Folder 55.5)
  - Craftsmanship, GWU - Alumni [6/7], undated (Box 2, Folder 55.6)
  - Craftsmanship, GWU - Alumni [7/7], undated (Box 2, Folder 55.7)
  - Joseph Baca, Richard E. Peck, GW Magazine Photo, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 56.1)
  - Joseph Fischetti & Winifred Coleman, GW Magazine Photo, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 56.2)
  - Dean East, GW Magazine Photo, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 56.3)
  - F. David Fowler, 09/09/1992 (Box 2, Folder 56.4)
  - Reunion, Group photo [1/7], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57.1)
  - Reunion, Group photo [2/7], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57.2)
  - Reunion, Group photo [3/7], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57.3)
  - Reunion, Group photo [4/7], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57.4)
  - Reunion, Group photo [5/7], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57.5)
  - Reunion, Group photo [6/7], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57.6)
  - Reunion, Group photo [7/7], 1989 (Box 2, Folder 57.7)
  - Koalo bear, Australian Adventure -Travel photos, undated (Box 2, Folder 58.1)
  - A giraffe, Australian Adventure -Travel photos, undated (Box 2, Folder 58.2)
  - Lanzarote, LasPalmas, Canary Islands, Travel photo, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 59.1)
  - Switzerland, Travel photo, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 59.2)
  - British Airways, Concorde, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 59.3)
  - Titlisbahn, Switzerland, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 59.4)
  - Reunion, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.1)
  - SPIA, Const. group, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.2)
  - Reunion, Pres. Elliott shaking hands with an alumna, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.3)
  - Reunion, Group of alumna, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.4)
  - Reunion, Nan B. Ward and others, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.5)
  - Reunion, Group photo [1/6], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.6)
  - Reunion, Group photo [2/6], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.7)
  - Reunion, Group photo [3/6], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.8)
  - Reunion, Group photo [4/6], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.9)
  - Reunion, Group photo [5/6], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.1)
  - Reunion, Group photo [6/6], 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.11)
  - Reunion, Dancing group, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.12)
  - Reunion, 10 Yr. party, 04/06/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.13)
  - Reunion, 25 Yr. party, GW Club, 04/06/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.14)
  - Reunion, 50 Year Luncheon, GW Club, 04/06/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.15)
  - Reunion, School Luncheons, 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.16)
  - Reunion, Reunion Gala, Omni Shoreham Hotel [1/2], 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.17)
  - Reunion, Reunion Gala, Omni Shoreham Hotel [2/2], 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.18)
  - Reunion, School Luncheons, SEAS (1-19), Reunion Gala (20-36), 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.19)
  - Reunion, 5 Yr. Party (1-22) School Luncheons, 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.2)
  - Reunion, School Luncheons, GW Club, 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.21)
  - Reunion, 50 Yr. Luncheon, GW Club, (1-19), 25 Yr., 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.22)
  - Reunion, Reunion Gala, Omni Shoreham Hotel [1/2], 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.23)
  - Reunion, Reunion Gala, Omni Shoreham Hotel [2/2], 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.24)
  - Reunion, 50 Yr. Luncheon, GW Club, 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.25)
  - Reunion, 10 Yr. Party, 5 Yr. Party, Women Sky's Top of, 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.26)
  - Strong Hall, SEHO, SEAS, (Tompkins), 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.27)
  - Reunion, 50 Yr. Luncheon, GW Club, 04/06/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.28)
  - Reunion, Reuion Gala, Omni Shoreham Hotel, 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.29)
  - Reunion, Reuion Gala, Omni Shoreham Hotel, 04/07/1990 (Box 2, Folder 60.3)
  - Prints from the 1991 Reunion Brochure, Building Scene (Box 2, Folder 61.1)
  - Buildings, from the 1991 Reunion Brochure, 12/1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.2)
  - Buildings, from the 1991 Reunion Brochure, 12/1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.3)
  - Alumnus looking at an album, Reunion Brochure, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.4)
  - Group dancing, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.5)
  - Man with daughter, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.6)
  - Group with the GW Mascot, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.7)
  - Two women dining, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.8)
  - Group chatting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61.9)
  - Alumni Photos, Group photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.1)
  - Alumni Photos, Woman's photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.2)
  - National Convention in Los Angeles, 06/1988 (Box 2, Folder 62.3)
  - Alumni Photos, Group photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.4)
  - Alumni Photos, Post Card, Cherry Arm Captains chair, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.5)
  - Alumni Photos, Group of bicyclists, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.6)
  - Alumni Photos, Two women with refreshments, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.7)
  - Alumni Photos, Man's photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.8)
  - Alumni Photos, Crew teams, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.9)
  - Alumni Photos, Concovation gathering at the Academic Center, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.1)
  - Alumni Photos, Basketball match, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.11)
  - Alumni Photos, Man's photo [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 62.12)
  - Alumni Photos, Man's photo [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 62.13)
  - Alumni Photos, Class of, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 62.14)
  - Alumni Photos, President Elliott with others [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 62.15)
  - Alumni Photos, President Elliott with others [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 62.16)
  - Alumni Photos, Group photo, 09/1987 (Box 2, Folder 62.17)
  - Alumni Photos, Dean Kelly and Harvey D. D. Snyder, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.18)
  - Alumni Photos, Group answering calls, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.19)
  - Alumni Photos, Robert C. Mahoney, M.D. '56, with John H. Jacobson, Jr., Hope College Inauguration, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.2)
  - Alumni Photos, Pres. Elliott passing through a parade of officers, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.21)
  - Alumni Photos, Pres. Elliott with the Univeristy Marshall, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.22)
  - Alumni Photos, University Yard, 10/1987 (Box 2, Folder 62.23)
  - Alumni Photos, A speaker, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.24)
  - Alumni Photos, Basketball match, undated (Box 2, Folder 62.25)
  - Alumni Chairs [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 63.1)
  - Alumni Chairs [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 63.2)
  - Alumni with refreshment, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.3)
  - Group photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.4)
  - Women's Basketball game, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.5)
  - Two alumni hand shaking, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.6)
  - A group photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.7)
  - Speaker and a gathering, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.8)
  - Soccer Match, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.9)
  - Female Soccer Player, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.1)
  - An orientation scene, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.11)
  - Group photo, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.12)
  - Jerald Jackson, Max Flank, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.13)
  - Two male members of the Colonials, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.14)
  - Subway scene, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.15)
  - Women's Volleyball, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.16)
  - A Couple, undated (Box 2, Folder 63.17)
  - An event [1/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 63.18)
  - An event [2/2], undated (Box 2, Folder 63.19)
  - Alumni Reunion Photos, Dining room scene, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.1)
  - Alumni Reunion Photos, Dean Kayser w. Walter Berton Law '14, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.2)
  - Alumni Reunion Photos, Graduates from '31 enter Mc Ballroom, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.3)
  - Alumni Reunion, Mary Connelly, LLB, '24, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.4)
  - Alumni Reunion, Dean Kayser chatting with others [1/2], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.5)
  - Alumni Reunion, Dean Kayser chatting with others [2/2], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.6)
  - Alumni Reunion, Reception 1st Day, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.7)
  - Alumni Reunion, Group photo, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.8)
  - Alumni Reunion, Pablo Silva of Phillipines receives award, 05/15/1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.9)
  - Alumni Reunion, Alumna receives an award, 05/15/1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.1)
  - Alumni Reunion, Campur Tour participants in Smith Center, 05/16/1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.11)
  - Alumni Reunion, Barbecue guests watch demonstration of Faka Firing, 05/16/1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.12)
  - Alumni Reunion, Brunch honoring Dean Kayser, 05/17/1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.13)
  - Alumni Reunion, Couple dancing (Henry Gragnan, Jr.), undated (Box 2, Folder 64.14)
  - Alumni Reunion, Different activities, groups [1/6], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.15)
  - Alumni Reunion, Different activities, groups [2/6], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.16)
  - Alumni Reunion, Different activities, groups [3/6], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.17)
  - Alumni Reunion, Different activities, groups [4/6], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.18)
  - Alumni Reunion, Different activities, groups [5/6], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.19)
  - Alumni Reunion, Different activities, groups [6/6], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64.2)
  - Reunion DAAA [1/2], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.1)
    1 Sleeve
  - Reunion DAAA [2/2], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.2)
  - Reunion DAAA, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.3)
  - Reunion DAAA, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.4)
  - Reunion DAAA, Male speaker, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.5)
  - Reunion DAAA, Group chatting, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.6)
  - Reunion DAAA, Group photo, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.7)
  - Reunion DAAA, An event, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.8)
  - Reunion DAAA, Female graduate with family and three babies, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.9)
  - Reunion DAAA, Group chatting, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.1)
  - Reunion DAAA, Two students with the GWU emblem, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.11)
  - Reunion DAAA, male speaker, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.12)
  - Reunion DAAA, Member signing an autograph, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.13)
  - Reunion DAAA, Display of oriental art works, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.14)
  - Reunion DAAA, Reception scene, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.15)
  - Reunion DAAA, Alumna with GW busts, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.16)
  - Reunion DAAA, Alumna with GW busts, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.17)
  - Reunion DAAA, Speaker and an audience, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.18)
  - Reunion DAAA, Member signing an autograph, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.19)
  - Reunion DAAA, A gathering scene [1/2], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.2)
  - Reunion DAAA, A gathering scene [2/2], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.21)
  - Reunion DAAA, A reception scene, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.22)
  - Reunion DAAA, A speaker, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.23)
  - Reunion DAAA, A group chatting, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.24)
  - Reunion DAAA, A speaker, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.25)
  - Reunion DAAA, A group, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.26)
  - Reunion DAAA, A gathering, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.27)
  - Reunion DAAA, Group of women chatting, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.28)
  - Reunion DAAA, Pair by the DAA, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.29)
  - Reunion DAAA, Welcome class of '62, '72, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.3)
  - Reunion DAAA, Three alumni, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.31)
  - Reunion DAAA, GWU Campus, 02/1982 (Box 2, Folder 65.32)
  - Reunion DAAA, Group of faculty [1/2], 05/10/1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.33)
  - Reunion DAAA, Group of faculty [2/2], 05/10/1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.34)
  - Reunion DAAA, Group by the DAAA, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.35)
  - Reunion DAAA, Graduates and families, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.36)
  - Reunion DAAA, Reception, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.37)
  - Reunion DAAA, An Insignia, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.38)
  - Reunion DAAA, A gathering, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.39)
  - Reunion DAAA, Oriental performance, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.4)
  - Reunion DAAA, Oriental performers, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.41)
  - Reunion DAAA, Two women by the DAAA, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.42)
  - Reunion DAAA, Speaker, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.43)
  - Reunion DAAA, An event, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 65.44)
  - Aerial View Photos of GWU and surroundings [1/3], undated (Box 2, Folder 66.1)
  - Aerial View Photos of GWU and surroundings [2/3], undated (Box 2, Folder 66.2)
  - Aerial View Photos of GWU and surroundings [3/3], undated (Box 2, Folder 66.3)
  - An event an groups, undated (Box 2, Folder 67.1)
  - Reception scene, undated (Box 2, Folder 67.2)
  - Reception after opening of GWU Theater season, 10/08/1985 (Box 2, Folder 67.3)
  - Different Scenes, undated (Box 2, Folder 67.4)
  - Events, undated (Box 2, Folder 67.5)
  - Gathering and groups, undated (Box 2, Folder 67.6)
  - GW Alumni [1/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.1)
  - GW Alumni [2/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.2)
  - GW Alumni [3/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.3)
  - GW Alumni [4/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.4)
  - GW Alumni [5/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.5)
  - GW Alumni [6/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.6)
  - GW Alumni [7/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.7)
  - GW Alumni [8/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.8)
  - GW Alumni [9/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.9)
  - GW Alumni [10/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 68.1)
  - GW Alumni [11/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.1)
  - GW Alumni [12/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.2)
  - GW Alumni [13/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.3)
  - GW Alumni [14/21], undated (Box 3, Folder 69.4)